endtransplantabuse.org 2019-06-26

# Privacy Policy | The International Coalition to End Transplant Abuse in China

### Privacy Policy

In this Privacy Policy, ‘us’ ‘we’ or ‘our’ means International Coalition to End Transplant  
Abuse in China Ltd. We are committed to respecting your privacy. Our Privacy Policy  
sets out how we collect, use, store and disclose your personal information. We are bound  
by the Australian Privacy Principles contained in the Privacy Act. 

By providing personal information to us, you consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy and any other arrangements that apply between us. We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time by publishing changes to it on our website. We encourage you to check our website periodically to ensure that you are aware of our current Privacy Policy.

Personal information includes information or an opinion about an individual that is reasonably identifiable. For example, this may include your name, age, gender, postcode and contact details.

##### **Personal information we may collect  
**

We may collect the following types of personal information: 

  * name;
  * mailing or street address;
  * city/state of residence;
  * profession; 
  * email address;
  * telephone number and other contact details;
  * your device ID, device type, geo-location information, computer and connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the sites, ad data, IP address and standard web log information;
  * details of the services we have provided to you or that you have enquired about, including any additional information necessary to deliver those services and respond to your enquiries;
  * any additional information relating to you that you provide to us directly through our website or app or indirectly through your use of our website or app or online presence or through other websites or accounts from which you permit us to collect information;
  * information you provide to us through customer surveys; or
  * any other personal information that may be required in order to facilitate your dealings with us.

We may collect these types of personal information either directly from you, or from thirdparties. We may collect this information when you:

  * register on our website or app;
  * communicate with us through correspondence, chats, email, or when you share information with us from other social applications, services or websites;
  * interact with our sites, services, content and advertising. In addition, when you agree to work together with us or volunteer with us we may collect certain information from you (including your name, contact details, and work history). This Privacy Policy does not apply to acts and practices in relation to employee records of our current and former employees, which are exempt from the Privacy Act.

##### **How we may use your personal information  
**

We may collect, hold, use and disclose your personal information for the following  
purposes: 

  * to enable you to access and use our website;
  * to operate, protect, improve and optimize our website, business and our users’ experience, such as to perform analytics, conduct research and for advertising and marketing; 
  * to send you service, support and administrative messages, reminders, technical notices, updates, security alerts, and information requested by you;
  * to send you marketing and promotional messages and other information that we think you may find interesting;
  * to administer rewards, surveys, contests, or other promotional activities or events sponsored or managed by us or our business partners;
  * to comply with our legal obligations, resolve any disputes that we may have with any of our users, and enforce our agreements with third parties; and 
  * to consider your employment application.

We may send you direct marketing communications and information about our services.  
This may take the form of emails, SMS, mail or other forms of communication, in  
accordance with the Spam Act and the Privacy Act. You may opt-out of receiving  
marketing materials from us by contacting us using the details set out below or by using  
the opt-out facilities provided. 

We may disclose personal information for the purposes described in this privacy policy  
to: 

  * our staff; 
  * professional advisers;
  * our sponsors or promoters of any competition that we conduct via our services; 
  * specific third parties authorized by you to receive information held by us; and/or
  * other persons, including government agencies, regulatory bodies and law enforcement agencies, or as required, authorized or permitted by law. 

##### **Disclosure of personal information outside Australia  **

We may disclose personal information outside of Australia to our staff or professional advisors, located in countries listed on our website. 

When you provide your personal information to us, you consent to the disclosure of your information outside of Australia and acknowledge that we are not required to ensure that overseas recipients handle that personal information in compliance with Australian Privacy Law. We will, however, take reasonable steps to ensure that any overseas recipient will deal with such personal information in a way that is consistent with the Australian Privacy Principles. 

##### **Using our website and cookies  **

We may collect personal information about you when you use and access our website. While we do not use browsing information to identify you personally, we may record certain information about your use of our website, such as which pages you visit, the time and date of your visit and the internet protocol address assigned to your computer. We may also use ‘cookies’ or other similar tracking technologies on our website that help us track your website usage and remember your preferences. Cookies are small files that store information on your computer, TV, mobile phone or other device. They enable the entity that put the cookie on your device to recognize you across different websites, services, devices and/or browsing sessions. You can disable cookies through your internet browser but our websites may not work as intended for you if you do so.

We may also use cookies to enable us to collect data that may include personal  
information. For example, where a cookie is linked to your account, it will be considered  
personal information under the Privacy Act. We will handle any personal information  
collected by cookies in the same way that we handle all other personal information as  
described in this Privacy Policy. 

##### **Security  
**

We may hold your personal information in either electronic or hard copy form. We take  
reasonable steps to protect your personal information from misuse, interference and loss,  
as well as unauthorized access, modification or disclosure and we use a number of  
physical, administrative, personnel and technical measures to protect your personal  
information. For example, we use the most current and secure online tools to store and  
transmit personal information as needed among our staff. However, we cannot guarantee  
the security of your personal information. 

##### **Links**

Our website may contain links to websites operated by third parties. Those links are  
provided for convenience and may not remain current or be maintained. Unless expressly  
stated otherwise, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of, or any content on,  
those linked websites, and have no control over or rights in those linked websites. The  
privacy policies that apply to those other websites may differ substantially from our  
Privacy Policy, so we encourage individuals to read them before using those websites. 

##### **Accessing or correcting your personal information  
**

You can access the personal information we hold about you by contacting us using the <https://endtransplantabuse.org/connect/>. Sometimes, we may not be able to provide you with access to all of your personal information and, where this is the case, we will tell you why. We may also need to verify your identity when you request your personal information.

If you think that any personal information we hold about you is inaccurate, please contact  
us and we will take reasonable steps to ensure that it is corrected. 

##### **Making a complaint  
**

If you think we have breached the Privacy Act, or you wish to make a complaint aboutthe way we have handled your personal information, you can contact us at this link:https://endtransplantabuse.org/connect/. Please include your name, email address and/ortelephone number and clearly describe your complaint. We will acknowledge yourcomplaint and respond to you regarding your complaint within a reasonable period of time. If you think that we have failed to resolve the complaint satisfactorily, we willprovide you with information about the further steps you can take.

##### **Contact Us  
**

For further information about our Privacy Policy or practices, or to access or correct your  
personal information, or make a complaint, please contact us using the details set out  
below: 

Legal Department  
International Coalition to End Transplant Abuse in China Ltd. <https://endtransplantabuse.org/connect/>

Effective: February 18, 2018
